segmentnext.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | SegmentNext

## Aksile Media Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. It is Aksile Media’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, [https://segmentnext.com](https://segmentnext.com/), and other sites we own and operate.

### Information We collect

#### Log Data

When you visit our website, we and our third party service providers (including any third-party content, advertising, and analytics providers) may automatically log the standard data provided by your web browser. This data is considered “non-identifying information”, as it does not personally identify you on its own. It may include your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and version, the pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on each page, your interaction with content or advertisements and other details.

We may also collect data about the device you are using to access our website. This data may include the device type, operating system, unique device identifiers, device settings, and geo-location data. What we collect can depend on the individual settings of your device and software. We recommend checking the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider to learn what information they make available to us.

#### Personal Data

You can visit the website without telling us who are you or giving us any information that can identify you personally. If, however, you want to register to become a member of the website to comment and use other community features, we may ask for personal Data, such as your:

  * Name
  * Email

This data is considered “identifying information”, as it can personally identify you. We only request personal data relevant to providing you with a service, use it to help provide or improve this service, to contact you with your consent, from time to time, including via email, about us, our products and services, or our partners.

In addition, you are required to submit certain personal data when you apply for a job. This data may include demographic information, information about your preferences and interests. You can choose not to submit any personal data but it will inhibit our ability to process your application.

### How we collect information

We collect information by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used. You are free to refuse our request for this information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services without it.

### Use of information

We may use a combination of identifying and non-identifying information to understand who our visitors are, how they use our services, and how we may improve their experience of our website in future. We do not disclose the specifics of this information publicly, but may share aggregated and anonymized versions of this information, for example, in website and customer usage trend reports.

We may use your personal details to contact you with updates about our website and services, along with promotional content that we believe may be of interest to you. If you wish to opt out of receiving promotional content, you can follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided alongside any promotional correspondence from us.

We may further use your personal information to administer and process contests, sweepstakes, and promotions. To tailor content, recommendations and advertisements with the help of third parties both on the website and elsewhere online.

Or for purposes as described at the time you provide your information, with your consent, and as further explained in this Privacy Policy.

### Data processing and storage

The information (Log Data and Personal Data) we collect is stored and processed where we (Pakistan) or our partners, affiliates and third-party providers (United States) maintain facilities. By using our Site, you consent to data transfer within jurisdictions subject to data protection laws that reflect our commitment to protecting the privacy of our users.

We only retain information for as long as necessary to provide a service, or to improve our services in future. While we retain this data, we will protect it within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. That said, we advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, and cannot guarantee absolute data security.

If you request your personal information be deleted, or where your personal information becomes no longer relevant to our operations, we will erase it from our system within a reasonable time-frame.

### Cookies and Tracking Technologies

We use “cookies” to collect information about you and your activity across our site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our website stores on your computer, and accesses each time you visit, so we can understand how you use our site. This helps us serve you content based on preferences you have specified. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for more information.

We use following types of cookies and tracking technologies for purposes set out below:

Analytics Tracking Cookies | These cookies are used to collect information about traffic to our website and users use our website. Information gathered doesn’t identify any individual visitor. It is aggregated information, all the data is anonymized. It includes number of visitors to the website, page(s) they visited, time spent on that page, next page they visited, when they visited the page(s), whether they have visited the website before, and other similar information. Analytics tracking gives us insight into user activity which is essential to the growth of the website. 

We use Google Analytics for this purpose. Google Analytics uses its own cookies. You can find more about Google Analytics cookies on: <https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies>

Interested in learning how Google protects your data?  Visit the designated Google page on the subject: [www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)

If you want to prevent us from tracking you by any means, you can download this browser plugin by Google – <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
  
---|---  
Essential and Functionality Cookies | Essential cookies are crucial to your experience of a website, enabling core features like user logins, account management, shopping carts and payment processing. We use essential cookies to enable certain functions on our website. 

Functional cookies allow us to remember your choices when you browse our website, for example, remembering your login details and remembering which intractable element on the website you have already interacted with. Functionality cookies are essential to provide you with more personal experience or to avoid the frustration of having to re-enter your preferences and choices every time you visit the website.  
  
Social Media Cookies | Every time you interact with our content on or off social media website like Facebook, Twitter, Google+, Reddit, your action is recorded by these social media websites.  
Targeting / Advertising Cookies | These cookies track your browsing habits to enable us to show you advertisements that you are more likely to interact with. These cookies use information about your browsing history to group you with users who have similar interests. Based on that information, and with our permission, third-party advertisers can place cookies to enable them to show advertisements relevant to your interests while you are on third-party websites. 

These cookies store your location, IP and region ID, which helps us show you locale-specific news and allows our services to operate more efficiently. However, you can disable these cookies by visiting; <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>

You can disable this form of advertisement by removing targeted or advertising cookies. However, you may not see advertisements that are relevant to your interests but you will see advertisements nonetheless.

Provided that you do choose to remove cookies by the companies listed at the above link, note that it doesn’t list all companies who are engaged in behavioral advertising, so you may still receive targeted ads relevant to your interests from companies that are not listed.  
  
**Flash Cookie**  
A Flash cookie is a data file placed on a device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that is built into or downloaded by you onto your device. Flash cookies are used for various purposes, including, without limitation, enabling a Flash feature and remembering your preferences. For more information about Flash and the privacy choices Adobe offers, visit <https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html>.

If you choose to adjust your Flash privacy settings on your device some features of the Services may not function properly.

**Pixel Tags**  
We also use pixel tags, small graphics files that allow us and third parties to monitor the use of the website and collect user activity information. A pixel tag installed on a page can collect information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page, URL of the page, the time (and length of time) the page containing the pixel tag was viewed; the type of browser that retrieved the pixel tag; and the identification number of any cookie previously placed by that server on your computer.

We use pixel tags, either provided by us or by our third-party advertisers, service providers and ad networks, to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with our website and Services and use them in combination with our cookies to provide offers and information of interest to you. Pixel tags also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit the Services or other websites.

For more information on use of cookies and similar technologies on our Site, you can read our [Cookie Policy](https://segmentnext.com/cookie-policy/). To read more on cookies in general, what cookies are set on your computer or mobile device and how to delete them, you can visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/> and <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk>. 

### How We Share Data

Generally we only share non-identifying data (Log Data, anonymous data, aggregated stats) with third party services (analytics companies, advertisers and ad agencies, data management and storage services) for the purpose of performing services essential to our operations, on our behalf. We do not share any personally identifying information with them without your explicit consent. We do not give them permission to disclose or use any of our data for any other purpose.

We may, from time to time, allow limited access to personal data to the extent to enable them to perform those services. Such services include Google analytics tracking and use of Google AMP Client ID API, each of which enables collection and sharing of your information (including Personal Data) with Google for further use. For particulars on Google’s usage of your information and how to control it, please see [How Google uses Data when you visit our Site](https://privacy.google.com/your-data.html) and [Google’s Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). 

We may share your data for the purpose of third-party marketing only when opt-in (You can always opt-out). Provided that you have consented to receive third party marketing messages we share your information with those third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. Messages delivered by third party will subject you to their own privacy policy. 

We will refuse government and law enforcement requests for data if we believe a request is too broad or unrelated to its stated purpose. However, we may cooperate if we believe the requested information is necessary and appropriate to comply with legal process, to protect our own rights and property, to protect the safety of the public and any person, to prevent a crime, or to prevent what we reasonably believe to be illegal, legally actionable, or unethical activity.

We do not otherwise share or supply personal information to third parties. We do not sell or rent your personal information to marketers or third parties.

### Anonymous Data

Anonymous data is the information that does not permit you to be identified or identifiable, either alone or when combined with any other information available to a third-party. We may create anonymous data from the Personal Data we receive about you and other individuals whose Personal Data we collect. 

Anonymous data will include analytics information and information collected by us using cookies. We make Personal Data into anonymous data by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We use this anonymous data to analyze usage patterns in order to make improvements to our Site. 

### Public Data

If you identify any User Information as public, you are authorizing us to share such information publicly. For example, you can make your alias, bio, email or photos publicly available on sections (comments, forums, user profiles) of the site where it is possible, automatically making it available to other users of the Site. You understand and agree that anyone can access, use, and disclose any information that you post to those sections of the Site.

### Advertising

We also use your data for advertising purposes. We use third-party advertising companies who serve ads to help keep content free. For these partners, we put additional restrictions on how your data can be used to prevent it from misuse. For instance, we do not allow these partners to take your information for profiling and personalizing ads on other sites. Please review the following for a full list of partners and purposes: <https://www.pubgalaxy.com/privacy-policy.html>

These companies collect and use click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over during your visits to the Services and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use tracking technologies to collect this information. Other companies’ use of their tracking technologies is subject to their own privacy policies.

Some of the third-party services providers and/or Advertisers may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the “opt-out” procedures of NAI members. You can opt-out of our use of your Web site viewing behavior data to serve you interest-based advertising on third-party sites and email newsletters here <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

If you are accessing the Site through an application (i.e., mobile phone or tablet) you can download the AppChoices application from your device’s application store (i.e., Google Play, Apple App Store, and Amazon Store). This DAA application allows participating companies to offer an opt-out of customized advertisements that are based on predictions about your interests generated from your application usage. For more information, visit <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices.>

Please note opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads while online or on your device.

### Children’s Privacy

Aksile Media, its affiliate publications and services are intended for general audience, not suitable for children under the age of 13. We do not collect any information from children under the age of 13. If a parent becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should immediately contact us to request deletion of such data. 

### Limits of our policy

This privacy policy only covers Aksile Media’s own collecting and handling of data. We only work with partners, affiliates and third-party providers whose privacy policies align with ours, however we cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of those sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.

### Changes to this policy

At our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to reflect current acceptable practices. We will take reasonable steps to let users know about changes via our Site. If you are a registered user on [https://segmentnext.com](https://segmentnext.com/), we will notify you using the contact details saved in your account. Your continued use of this site after any changes to this policy will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information.

### Your rights and responsibilities

As our user, you have the right to be informed about how your data is collected and used. You are entitled to know what data we collect about you, and how it is processed. You are entitled to correct and update any personal information about you, and to request this information be deleted. You may amend or remove your account information at any time, using the tools provided in your account or by contacting us using details provided below.

You are entitled to restrict or object to our use of your data, while retaining the right to use your personal information for your own purposes. You have the right to opt out of data about you being used in decisions based solely on automated processing.

Feel free to contact us if you have any concerns or questions about how we handle your data and personal information.

**Aksile Media**  
Aksile Media  
126-H Model Town, Lahore, Pakistan  
contact@segmentnext.com

This policy is effective as of 24 May 2018.
